Wallen, Saul Papers 5012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- B.F. Goodrich Co. (Akron), 1952-1965 (Box 106)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision F-222), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 53)
    May 14, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-10), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 54)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision F-223), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 55)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-13), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 56)
    June 4, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision F-225), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 57)
    June 23, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-22), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 58)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-23), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 59)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-24), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 60)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-25), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 61)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-26), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 62)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-27), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 63)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-28), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 64)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-29), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 65)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-30), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 66)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-31), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 67)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-33), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 68)
    June 24, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-37), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 69)
    August 15, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-38), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 70)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-39), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 71)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-40), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 72)
    August 16, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-42), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 73)
    August 19, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-43), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 74)
    August 24, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-44), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 75)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-45), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 76)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-50), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 77)
    August 29 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-51), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 78)
    September 19, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-52), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 79)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-11), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 80)
    September 25. 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-56), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 81)
    September 28, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-61), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 82)
    October 8, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-62), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 83)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-66), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 84)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-63), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 85)
    October 11, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-68), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 86)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-60), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 87)
    October 12, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-64), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 88)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-65), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 89)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-67), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 90)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision F-228), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 91)
    October 15, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-69), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 92)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-71), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 93)
    October 30, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-76), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 94)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-77), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 95)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision F-229), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 96)
    November 25, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-83), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 97)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-78), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 98)
    November 27, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-82), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 99)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-85), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 100)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-84), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 101)
    November 28, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-88), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 102)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-80), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 103)
    November 29, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-81), 1953 (Box 106, Folder 104)
- B.F. Goodrich Co. (Akron), 1952-1965 (Box 107)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-123, 1953 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-101, 1953 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-111, 1953 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-125, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-126, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-201, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-202, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 14017 Decision G-213, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Petition 13200-6655, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 14559 Decision G-269, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision F-227, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-102, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-103, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-104, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-101-A, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-105, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-106, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-107, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-108, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-109, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-110, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-112, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-113, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 23)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 G-110, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 24)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-79, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 25)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 G-117, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 26)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-118, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 27)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-124, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 28)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 G-122, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 29)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 G-127, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 30)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 G-128, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 31)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-129, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 32)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-130, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 33)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-131, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 34)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-132, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 35)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-121, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 36)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 G-120, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 37)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-138, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 38)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision F-226, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 39)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-133, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 40)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-137, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 41)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 434 Decision G-141, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 42)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-142, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 43)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 G-146, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 44)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 G-147, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 45)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 G-143, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 46)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-145, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 47)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-144, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 48)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-150, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 49)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-151, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 50)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-169, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 51)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13729 Decision G-148, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 52)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13610 Decision G-149, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 53)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13651 Decision G-152, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 54)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13629 Decision G-254, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 55)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13825 Decision G-166, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 56)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13730 Decision G-195, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 57)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13907 Decision G-168, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 58)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 12915 Decision G-163, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 59)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13421 Decision G-164, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 60)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13275 Decision G-165, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 61)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13641 Decision G-167, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 62)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13402 Decision G-171, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 63)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13719 Decision G-172, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 64)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13715 Decision G-165, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 65)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13996 Decision G-176, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 66)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-41, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 67)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13890 Decision G-177, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 68)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13945 Decision G-178, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 69)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13833 Decision G-179, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 70)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13735 Decision G-199, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 71)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13831 Decision G-196, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 72)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 14010 Decision G-197, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 73)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Petition 13949 Decision G-198, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 74)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 14092 Decision G-200, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 75)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-210, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 76)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-211, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 77)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-212, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 78)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-220, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 79)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-215, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 80)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-216, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 81)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-217, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 82)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-218, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 83)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-219, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 84)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Decision G-221, 1954 (Box 107, Folder 85)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 14047 Decision G-234, 1955 (Box 107, Folder 86)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 13584 Decision G-235, 1955 (Box 107, Folder 87)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 14108 Decision G-237, 1955 (Box 107, Folder 88)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 14394, 14396, 14397 Decision G-238, 1955 (Box 107, Folder 89)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 14028 Decision G-239, 1955 (Box 107, Folder 90)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Co. and URCLPWA Local 5 Pet. 14188 Decision G-236, 1955 (Box 107, Folder 91)
- B.F. Goodrich Co. (Akron), 1952-1965 (Box 108)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5, 1953 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-240), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    February 5, 1955
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-241), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-242), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-243), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    March 23, 1955
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-244), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-245), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-246), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-247), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-248), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-249), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-251), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    April 4, 1955
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-256), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    April 18, 1955
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-257), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision G-255), 1955 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    April 19, 1955
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5, 1960 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision J-22), 1961 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    January 16, 1961
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision J-23), 1961 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    January 25, 1961
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision J-28), 1961 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    February 27, 1961
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision J-29), 1961 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    February 28, 1961
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision J-31), 1961 (Box 108, Folder 21)
    March 3, 1961
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision J-30), 1961 (Box 108, Folder 22)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision J-41), 1961 (Box 108, Folder 23)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision J-55), 1961 (Box 108, Folder 24)
    July 6, 1961
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision J-71), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 25)
    February 7, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision K-1), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 26)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision J-72), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 27)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision J-73), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 28)
    February 8, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision H-177), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 29)
    February 10, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision J-75), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 30)
    March 20, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision K-3), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 31)
    March 21, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision K-4), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 32)
    March 22, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision I-83), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 33)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision I-85), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 34)
    May 9, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision I-86), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 35)
    May 18, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision K-8), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 36)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision K-7), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 37)
    May 19, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision K-9), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 38)
    May 20, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision K-10), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 39)
    May 21, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 318 (Decision K-18), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 40)
    August 21, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision K-19), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 41)
    August 30, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision K-20), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 42)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Akron, Ohio) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5 (Decision K-21), 1962 (Box 108, Folder 43)